Finding Aid for the James Arkatov Photographs PASC.0340.Coll-level-DAO
UCLA Library Special Collections
James Arkatov photographs
circa 1940-circa 2000
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0340
4.0 Linear Feet (8 boxes containing 2975 photographs)
The collection consists of photographs of musicians and fine artists taken by the cellist, James Arkatov. The photographs are in the process of being digitized. The finding aid will continue to be updated as the digital files become available.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9966371123606533
Biographical Note
Jim Arkatov has had distinguished careers as a musician and photographer. He was born in Odessa, Russia and left with his family at an early age for San Francisco, where he developed as a child prodigy and gave his debut cello recital at age 14. At age 18, he was invited by Fritz Feiner to join the Pittsburgh Symphony. Later, he joined the San Francisco Symphony with Pierre Monteux, and went on to be principal cellist of the Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra under Fabien Sevitzky.
Arkatov returned to California in 1946 as a freelance musician in major studios of Hollywood and was later appointed principal cellist of the NBC Symphony Orchestra. Continuing his solo activities, he appeared in the Monday Evening Concert Series. In 1956, he married Salome Ramras, and they performed a piano-cello duo, performing in concerts throughout California. In 1968, he founded the Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra and was its first principal cellist.
He had begun his photographic career when he was with the Pittsburgh Symphony. In 1990, these photographs became the basis of his first book, "Masters of Music." In 1998, he published his second book, "Artists: The Creative Personality." He has permanent and rotating exhibits of his photographs at the Colburn School of Music, the Cedar-Sinai Hospital and the Doheny Library of the University of Southern California.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of photographs of jazz musicians performing in the Los Angeles area; classical musicians, and fine artists taken by cellist, James Arkatov.
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1. Jazz Musicians
Series 2. Classical Musicians
Series 3. Fine Artists
- Classical Musicians, Series 2.
  - Afanasieff, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    Scope and Contents note
    3 photographs
  - Alizadeh, Hossein, 2007; 4 x 6, b & w, color (Box 6)
    22 photographs
  - Andre, Maurice, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    2 photographs
  - Arkatov, James, 2006; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
    2 photographs. With unidentified man.
  - Arrau, Claudio, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Arrau, Claudio, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Arrau, Claudio, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Arrau, Claudio, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Asawa, Brian, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Ashkenazy, Vladimir, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    6 photographs
  - Ashkenazy, Vladimir, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Ax, Emanuel, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    with Isaac Stern in background
  - Ax, Emanuel, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    4 photographs
  - Ax, Emanuel, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Badura-Skoda, Paul, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    7 photographs
  - Balakrishan, Iyer, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Barta, Jiri, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Barta, Jiri, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Beecham, Sir Thomas, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Beecham, Sir Thomas, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Bell, Joshua, 2008; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Bell, Joshua, 2008; 3 x 5, b & w (Box 6)
    8 photographs
  - Bell, Joshua, 2008; 6 x 6, b & w (Box 6)
  - Bell, Joshua, 2008; 8.5 x 8, b & w (Box 6)
  - Bellare, Ravi, 1993; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
  - Bernstein, Leonard, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Boulez, Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    12 photographs
  - Brendel, Alfred, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Bronfman, Yefim, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Brown, Earle, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Brown, Ray, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Browning, John, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    4 Photographs
  - Browning, John, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Bylsma, Anner, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Carter, Elliott, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Carter, Elliott, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    General note
    At Ojai.
  - Casadesus, Robert, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Casadesus, Robert, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1956; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1956; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    with James Arkatov
  - Ciccolini, Aldo, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    5 photographs
  - Cliburn, Van, 1960; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    with Rosina Lhevinne
  - Copland, Aaron, 1960; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Das Gupta, Buddhadev, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Das Gupta, Buddhadev, 1993; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
  - Davidovich, Bella, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Dicterow, Glenn, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Fleck, Bela, 2004 January; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Fleck, Bela, 2004 January; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
    With Jeffrey Kahane.
  - Fleck, Bela, 2004 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Fleck, Bela, 2004 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Fleischer, Leon, 1959; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Fleischer, Leon, 1959; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    with Pierre Monteaux
  - Fleischer, Leon, 1977; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Fleisher Quartet, 2004 March; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Fleisher Quartet, 2004 March; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Fleisher, Leon, 2003 January; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Fleisher, Leon, 2003 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
    20 photographs
  - Fliter, Ingrid, 2009; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Fliter, Ingrid, 2009; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Francescatti, Zino, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Francescatti, Zino, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Gasparyn, Djivan, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Gavrilov, Andrei, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
    10 photographs. In rehearsal at Disney Hall.
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
    17 photographs. In rehearsal at Disney Hall.
  - Gergiev, Valery, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Gergiev's Boris Godunov, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
    12 photographs.
  - Gergiev's Boris Godunov, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
    15 photographs. In rehearsal.
  - Gilels, Emil, 1965; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Glass, Philip, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Gorecki, Henryk, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Grappelli, Stephane, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Greenhouse, Bernard, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Greenhouse, Bernard, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
  - Gutierrez, Horacio, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Hampton, Lionel, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Han, Tong Il, 1993 (Box 5)
    6 photographs.One photograph with Salome Arkatov.
  - Harrel, Lynn, 1980; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    2 photographs, with Brooks Smith
  - Haslop, Clayton, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1957; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1966; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    3 photographss, with Brooks Smith
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1966; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Horowitz, Vladimir, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Isserlis, Steve, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Karr, Gary, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Khan, Ali Akbar, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Khan, Ali Akbar, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Khan, Ustad Shujaat, 2006; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Khan, Ustad Shujaat, 2006; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Khevinne, Rosina, 1960; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    With Brooks Smith
  - Kissin, Evgeny, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Klein, Walter, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Kondrashin, Kirill, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Koussevitsky, Serge, 1957; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Kraggerud, Henning, 2004 September; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    In performance with V. Bakadeinikoff, conductor.
  - Kremer, Gidon, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Kuerti, Anton, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Lang Lang, 2001 September; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Laredo, Jaime, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    With: Cho-Liang Lin, Mark Peskanov and Gil Shaham. Three photographs.
  - Laredo, Jaime, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Lewis, John, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Lin, Cho-Liang, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 3.5 x 5.5 b & w (Box 5)
    9 photographs
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    10 photographs
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    7 photographs. One photograph with Emmanuel Ax.
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 3.5 x 5.5 b & w (Box 5)
    At UCSC master class. 20 photographs
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 1998 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Mackerras, Sir Charles, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Marriner, Neville, 2008; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - McGegan, Nicholas, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Mehta, Mehli, 1998; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
  - Mehta, Mehli, 2001 November; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Mehta, Mehli, 1998; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 50)
  - Mehta, Zubin, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Mehta, Zubin, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2004 January; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2004 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2004 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2004 January; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2004 January; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Midori, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Midori, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Monteaux, Pierre, 1959; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    3 Photographs
  - Montoya, Carlos, 1985; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Mravinsky, Yevgeny, 1956; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    with the Leningrad Philharmonic Orchestra in Vienna
  - Murphy, Mark, 2009; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Newman, Anthony, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Newman, Anthony, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - O'Connor, Mark, 2008; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - O'Connor, Mark, 2008; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - O'Connor, Mark, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Oistrakh, David, 1956 (Box 3)
    with the Leningrad Philharmonic Orchestra conducted by Yevgeny Mravinsky in Vienna.
  - Oistrakh, David, 1965; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Paratore, Joe, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    With brother, Tony Paratore.
  - Parkening, Chris, 2006; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
    With Jubilant Sykes
  - Parkening, Chris, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Parkening, Chris, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
    Three photographs.
  - Parkening, Chris, 2006; 3 x 5, b & w (Box 6)
    With Jubilant Sykes. Four photographs.
  - Peck, Gregory, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    At the piano.
  - Peskanov, Mark, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    In performance with Fritz Reiner, conductor.
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1976; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Pollini, Maurizio, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Powell, Mel, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Quasthoff, Thomas, 1999 March; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Queen Ida, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Racy, Ali Jihad, 1999 March (Box 6)
  - Radu, Lupu, 1990; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    6 photos
  - Rampal, Jean Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Rampal, Jean Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Rampal, Jean Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Rampal, Jean Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    With camera
  - Rampal, Jean Pierre, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Reiner, Fritz, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Reiner, Fritz, 1948; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Riley, Terry, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Riley, Terry, 1994; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 2004 April; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 2004 April; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Rodriguez, Santiago, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 1956; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    With Jean Pierre Rampal
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 6)
    8 photographs. Some with Mehli Mehta.
  - Rubenstein, Arthur, 1957; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    3 photographs, with Serge Koussevitzky
  - Rubenstein, Arthur, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Sabicas, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Salonen, Esa Pekka, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Salonen, Esa Pekka, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 6)
  - Salonen, Esa Pekka, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 6)
  - Sanderling, Kurt, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Schnabel, Artur, 1947; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Segal, Steve, 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
  - Segovia, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    3 photographs, in masterclass with unidentified students
  - Seito Cello Group, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Seth, Pandit R., 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Sgouros, Dmitri, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Shaham, Gil, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Shaham, Gil, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Shujaat, Khan, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Slomninsky, Nicolas, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    7 photographs. Slomninsky's 99th birthday.
  - Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1994; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    7 photographs. One photograph with Salome Arkatov.
  - Smith, Brooks, 1960; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Starker, Janos, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Starker, Janos, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Steinberg, William, 1957; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stern Quartet, 2000 February; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Stern, Isaac, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stern, Isaac, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
    With Esa Pekka Salonen
  - Stern, Isaac, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Stern, Isaac, 2002 November (Box 6)
    14 photographs
  - Stern, Issac, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    with Yefim Bronfman
  - Stern, Issac, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stevenson, Robert, 2008; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Stevenson, Robert, 2008; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1955; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    With Castelnuovo-Tedesco.
  - Subramaniam, 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 5)
    7 photographs. With Steve Segal, guitar.
  - Subramaniam, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Subramaniam, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 6)
  - Suk, Joseph, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Suk, Joseph, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Suk, Joseph, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Suk, Joseph, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Swenson, Joseph, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Sykes, Jubilant, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
  - Szeryng, Henryk, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
    7 photographs, with accompanist Reiner
  - Szigeti, Joseph, 1950; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Thomas, Michael Tilson, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Toch, Ernst, 1964; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Toradze, Alexander, 2006; 8 x 10, color (Box 6)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Tully, Caitlin, 2005 February; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Unidentified Bassists, 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Unidentified Cellist, 2006; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
    2 photographs. Gergiev Orchestra 1st cellist.
  - Van Cliburn, 1958; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Walter, Bruno, 1949; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Want, Yujia, 2003 July; 3.5 x 5.5, color (Box 6)
  - Watts, Andre, 1986; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 3)
  - Yun, Chee, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
  - Yun, Chee, 2006; 4 x 6, color (Box 6)
  - Yun, Chee, 2006; 4 x 6, b & w (Box 6)
  - Zeltser, Mark, 2000 November; 8 x 10, b & w (Box 6)
  - Zuckerman, Eugenia, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 5)
  - Zuckerman, Pinchas, 2006; 3 x 5, color (Box 6)
  - Zuckerman, Pinchas, 2006; 4 x 6, b & w (Box 6)
    10 Photographs.
- Jazz Musicians, Series 1.
  - Abercrombie, John, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Acuna, Claudia, 2002 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Acuna, Claudia, 2002 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Acuna, Claudia, 2002 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Acuna, Claudia, 2002 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Monty, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Monty, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Monty, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Allison, Mose, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Allison, Mose, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Allyson, Karrin, 1999 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Allyson, Karrin, 1999 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alpert, Herb, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alpert, Herb, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Alpert, Herb, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Ernestine, 1996 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Ernestine, 1996 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Keith, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Barron, Kenny, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Barron, Kenny, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Barron, Kenny, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bellson, Louie, 1995 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bellson, Louie, 1995 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Benecke, Tex, 1996 May 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    At the Palladium.
  - Benecke, Tex, 1996 May 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Tony, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Tony, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Tony, 1998 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Walter, 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Walter Jr., 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Walter Jr., 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Blade, Brian, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Possibly drummer Brian Blade.
  - Blade, Brian, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Possible Brian Blade.
  - Bley, Paul, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bley, Paul, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bley, Paul, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bley, Paul, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bone Soir, 1999 July 31; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - BoneSoir, 1999 July 31; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Braden, Don, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Don Braden
  - Braden, Don, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brashear, Oscar, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Harold Land (saxophonist) and unidentified trombonist.
  - Brashear, Oscar, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brashear, Oscar, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Harold Land on saxophone
  - Brashear, Oscar, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Harold Land on saxophone.
  - Bresler, Fishel, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bresler, Fishel, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bresler, Fishel, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bresler, Fishel, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brignola, Nick, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Payne, Putter Smith and Joe La Barbera.
  - Brignola, Nick, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brignola, Nick, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Payne.
  - Brignola, Nick, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Charles, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Charles, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, James, 1996 May 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, James, 1996 May 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Oscar III, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Oscar III, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Oscar Jr., 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Oscar Jr., 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ray, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ray, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ray, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ray, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ray, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bryant, Bobby, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Buddy Collette and company, 1996 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Buddy Collette Group, 2000 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Buddy Collette Group, 2000 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Bunnett, Jane, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Larry Cramer.
  - Burrell, Kenny, 1997 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Burrell, Kenny, 1997 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Capp, Frankie, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Capp, Frankie, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Benny, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Benny, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Darryl Hall
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Regina, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Carter, Ron, 1996 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Scott Mayo.
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Scott Mayo, 2 copies.
  - Caymmi, Dori, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chancler, Ndugu, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Charlap, Bill, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Cheatham, Jeannie, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Cyrus, 1996 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Childs, Billy, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Christlieb, Pete, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Ernie Watts and Rickey Woodward in the recording studio.
  - Christlieb, Pete, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Ernie Watts and Rickey Woodward.
  - Christlieb, Pete, 1997 March; 3.5 x 5.5 color (Box 2)
  - Christlieb, Pete, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Claxton, Bill, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Claxton, Bill, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Claxton, Bill, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Clayton Brothers, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Clayton Brothers, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Clayton, John, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Clayton, John, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Clayton, John, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Clayton with unidentified musician.
  - Clayton, John, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Milt Jackson
  - Cochran, Todd, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)